Next up is to powder the skin now I know a lot of older women like more mature women do not like to wear powder they feel like it sets in there lines but there is a lot of new powders with finer texture that do not settle into lines.
It is imperative that you wear powder just to set the foundation it is going to keep in place all day.
So I like to use a loose powder.
Press powder just for touching up in your purse.
A loose powder you just want to gently brush it over the skin.
I just have a little extra powder there and definitely do not be heavy handed with powder.
Just a light sweeping and then remember what I said about putting the powder on top of the concealer you definitely want to take a sponge and you are actually going to press it on.
If you just dust it on with a brush it doesn't work as effectively but when you use a sponge it actually will help keep that oil in place.
So as you can see perfectly powder and still looking like herself.
Her gorgeous self.